好的，现在来使用这个同步adapter，这个过程跟之前的
Well, we're now using the sync adapter, and things are
工作差不多一样。我们希望这个应用能够
working pretty much as before. We want the app to do
很好的进行同步，同时我们不想再使用
this synchronization cleverly, and we'd like to get rid of
原来菜单里的刷新按钮。让我们把其他这些我们需要同步的活动
that old Refresh menu item. Let's start by cleaning up all
整理一下。我们其实并不需要
the other routines we have to sync. So we certainly
像FetchWeatherTask所需完成的工作，还有些类似在
don't need any of this other stuff like FetchWeatherTask, or all
Sunshine 服务要完成的任务， 同时我们需要把manifest 文件进行相应
this stuff we did in Sunshine service, and we'll want to clean
清理一下。这些东西我们都用不着了。
up the manifest accordingly. We certainly don't need either one of
在偏好设置中，我们则可以立即把它设
these anymore. And in Preferences, we can just change
置成同步。这样我们就能够在任何地方使用
that to sync immediately. So now we're really using this
同步adapter。现在看看，似乎还有一点问题，我们似乎并不是那么
sync adapter everywhere. We have a problem though. We're not
明智。用户在使用排序之后依旧看到
being very smart. The user still has all sorts of
一个空白的列表。我们希望的是同步能够更加智能。
places where they see an empty list. We want to
在安卓2.2之后，安卓添加了一个周期性同步的
sync more intelligently. In Android 2.2 Froyo, Android added the
功能。我们可以添加一个helper方法
ability to have sync adapter's sync periodically. We can add
到syncAdapter中。
a helper method to do this in our sync adapter.
问题是，这个方法并不是跟我们所期待的一样
The problem is, this method isn't as smart as
聪明，它并不能准确的提示用户
we'd like it to be, it still won't do all
并且在后台分批完成任务。
that cool batching with exact repeating alarms that we'd
庆幸的是，我们这里增加了实现这个需求的代码。
like it to. Fortunately, we've added something that does just
不过在API level 19之后是不支持的。
that, but it's not available until API level 19.
为了利用弹性时间处理非精确的重复警告，
Taking advantage of flexible time to do inexact repeating arms,
我们要在Sunshine同步adapter 中设置一些适当的默认值。
let's set some nice defaults for our Sunshine sync adapter.
首先，我们添加这些常量。为了让我们的代码更
First we'll add these constants. To make things a little
清楚，我们需要增加另一个函数，
clearer in our code let's add another function
当新的账户被创建以后来让我们调用。
that we'll call when a new account is created,
然后我们将设置一些重要的flag。就像
and here we'll set some important flags. Such as
configurePeriodicSync，这个我们刚好
configurePeriodicSync, the one we
创建的。SetSyncAutomatically，没有这个设置我们的
just created. SetSyncAutomatically, without which
周期同步就没法被激活。既然这个刚刚开始
our periodic sync will not be enabled. Since we're
让我们来执行一个同步处理，然后我们
just starting off let's do an immediate sync, then
可以从strategic调用它，并且获得一个
we can call it from a strategic place and
同步账户。最后，
get sync account. Finally, we can make the interface
通过添加一个initializeSyncAdapter 函数，
to the world a little bit cleaner by
我们可以使UI更加简洁
adding an initializeSyncAdapter function. That's simply makes sure
这就确保了账户被成功建立了。现在，
that an account has been created. And now
我们来看一下main Activity里的onCreate函数，
inside of the main activity in the onCreate, we
我们可以在这里面调用刚刚创建的新函数
can just make a call to that new
同时它会确保
function. And it'll make sure that the parameters for
我们对syncAdapter所传递的参数是正确的。
our sync adapter are set up correctly. Lets
让我们打开模拟器来看看这些有什么影响。
see if this has any impact on our emulator.
新的版本的Sunshine在一开始就显示了所有的
The new version of Sunshine right from the start shows all of current
天气。要使syncAdapter能够成功地
weather. For a sync with a sync
在后台进行周期性的同步操作，
adapter to happen successfully at periodic intervals
你需要一个可同步的ContentProvider
in the background you must: have a
为SyncAdapter开启自动同步
ContentProvider marked as syncable, enable automatic sync
初始化immediate sync
for the SyncAdapter, do an initial immediate
最后设置一个同步的间隔时间
sync, or set an interval in milliseconds.